<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title></title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Vultures 1 Album Review</title>
        <published>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;cdn.discordapp.com&amp;#x2F;attachments&amp;#x2F;1112522475788566629&amp;#x2F;1206765359546241085&amp;#x2F;Screenshot_20240211-165847.jpg?ex=65dd32d2&amp;amp;is=65cabdd2&amp;amp;hm=60a57d9b89a741fe1062aa856f46dbed27724ea3f35be62c0c37d4b89c9ef983&amp;amp;&quot; alt=&quot;Vultures 1&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After many delays Kanye West next collabration album with Ty Dolla $ign is here with the first volume of the Vultures trilogy. My opinions on the album is that there are some songs on here that are a miss for me and should’ve been cut out, replaced, or needed more fixing on, there is a lot of hits for me that makes the album enjoyable still. This project feels like a combination of Kanye’s past albums and eras that is sprinkled in the songs that I enjoyed the most, which I was totally surprised that he would go back to those sounds, ranging from the 2000s era with the College trilogy and 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreaks, to the 2010s era with MBDTF, Yeezus, TLOP, and much more. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt; First Act of VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
Right out with the intro, with STARS, is a really well done introduction to the album with really good drums which I assume JPEGMAFIA worked on for the intro as its really dynamic. Throughout the 1st act of the album, there are some songs that I didn&#x27;t really enjoy like KEYS TO MY LIFE AND HOODRAT but the rest of the 1st act like PAID, TALKING, BACK TO ME, DO IT. The disco&#x2F;dance and EDM aspect for the album like PAID AND DO IT is really executed well. I esspecially liked the violins and strings sounds in DO IT. 
&lt;h1&gt;Second Act of VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
Now the second act is my favorite part of the album starting with PAPERWORK, with its experimental aspects and distorted bass and drums, which has that YEEZUS sound really shine in this album with experimental voxstoo. And we transition from that experimental sound to straight 2000s nostalgic Kanye era. Now BURN takes the cake for being my most favorite track out of this album, with Kanye bringing back that classic flow and the amazing chorus that sounds like it&#x27;s a predecessor from his other song that last time we got this type of style of a song from him, White Dress. BURN makes me feel like I&#x27;m in sometype of cinematic Martial Arts&#x2F;Bruce Lee&#x2F;Quentin Tarantino movie type of vibe. This track is overall fun, soulful and simplistic but sounds amazing. I feel like if JPEGMAFIA helped produced this track, combinding soulful with a little bit more of experimental sounds and seeing how well that goes together. Would be something different I&#x27;ll like to see next time if Kanye or anyone (or even me) combines the two like that. The only con for this song is that its too short, ending at 1:51 minutes. Could&#x27;ve been more extended I feel. Though I do hope Kanye brings more of this sounds and make an album surrounded by the idea of BURN and White Dress. Then the next track FUK SUMN, goes back into that experimental hip-hop, with again, JPEGMAFIA helping producing this track with the chipmuck high pitch Kanye vocal sample and the complex drum patterns. After FUCK SUMN we go into the single with VULTURES, which when listening to the first version of it back in 2023, I didn&#x27;t really liked it at all, I thought it was too basic with the beat and the production, lyrics were okay though, the song has grown on me, but for sure not the best on this album when its competing other better songs mentioning before. With CARNIVAL, I love the choir sample having more of a Middle Eastern sounding throughout this song, with again more experimental trap. A little too dark with my taste as I don&#x27;t really like Playboi Carti&#x27;s music at all because of that. But still a hype type of song neither the less. 
&lt;h1&gt;Third act of the VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
With GOOD (DON&#x27;T DIE) is an absolute skip for me. Should&#x27;ve been cut and sounds like it needs more fixed on. It sures has 808s &amp; Heartbreaks sounding to it but to me wasn&#x27;t executed very well along with the singing and vocals sounded like it needs improvement. The last two songs in the third act is a lot better with BEG FORGIVENESS and KING. I also liked the sample chopping in the 3:39 mark of the song with BEG FORGIVENESS and has better singing. And again with KING, the drums in the production is amazing, and the line with &quot;Crazy, bipolar, antisemite&quot; makes me laugh with the way Kanye says it. Overall, I enjoyed this album despite it being flawed in many aspects, it somewhat feels like an album that is jotting down many ideas, concepts and genres with really strong ideas and ones that don&#x27;t work. Maybe that will be fixed in VULTURES 2 &amp; 3. 
&lt;h1&gt;Favorite Tracks&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BURN&lt;&#x2F;li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;FUCK SUMN&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TALKING&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAPERWORK&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DO IT&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STARS&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAID&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CARNIVAL&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BACK TO ME&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BEG FORGIVENESS&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KING&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Least Favorite Tracks&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GOOD (GOOD DON&#x27;T DIE)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HOODRAT&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KEYS TO MY LIFE&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VULTURES&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Final Verdict&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Going through the Dark Night of The Soul. Why is this Happening?</title>
        <published>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/">&lt;p&gt;Going through the Dark Night of the Soul, can sometimes feel pretty scary… the way that we’ve perceived life is crumbling before our eyes. Everything from what we believed is to be to being revealed what the truth is either in our personal lives or looking what society is. All of these multiple factors were the reason why the Dark Night of the Soul happened to me. But why does this happen in the first place anyways? Is it because of those external factors that we may think is the reason why it’s all happening and blame the outside, or is it because that we chose to experience this in order to grow? When researching this topic and coming to that conclusion that I, myself either unconsciously or consciously chose to go through this in order to get rid of the beliefs that didn’t serve me. Which made all the sense to me, because I chose the path of questioning myself, reality and this world. I consciously chose to pursue spirituality and self development to connect with myself even more. Which the outcome of this was a feeling of being born again, spiritual bliss and life was amplified even more. It was like I put on a pair of lenses that made me see life as this beautiful thing, from the trees, to the animals, the connection I’ve had and what not. But, this comes with the price of needing to know what the truth of this world or Matrix is. From seeing what the knowledge you’ve gained as a gift, to now looking at it as a curse. When 2020 happened, that’s when I had to face the reality and consciously decided to look into “conspiracies”, who was behind the pandemic, wars, killings and things that have been enslaving humanity for centuries. With me wanting to know the truth and refusing the pretty lies, I’ve gotten what I’ve want. Thus the way I’ve conveyed on what reality is as a kid, having to question even more on the matter, I realize it is a necessary part on one’s spiritual path and self development. Along with other factors taking place like separation I had from my friends because of lockdowns and not aligning with them anymore, as I’ve questioned the very things that is hard to come to terms with, but it’s needed. But most importantly being in separation from the girl that I’ve liked from the time, trying to reach out to keep our connection alive as the result was her admitting to avoided me, ghosting, running away and feelings of unrequited love, even though I still felt her presence when we weren’t talking at that time. All these factors, made me realize that I was in the Dark Night of the Soul. All I can say is to be patient on whatever you may have to face that you’ve may have been unconsciously running your whole life or seeing things not being the same anymore. That’s what I most importantly feel but I promise, that things will get better, even if it seems bleak, keeping facing that feeling of hopelessness, heartbreak, fears etc. and integrating that shadow. Realize that you were and always are a complete whole being, this too shall past. Be self forgiving and have self patience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Love Stars (Epilogue)</title>
        <published>2023-06-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-06-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/love-stars/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/love-stars/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/love-stars/">&lt;p&gt;here we are&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;my scars turned into actual Love Stars&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this time,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it isn’t love that is unrequited&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but it’s very alive and excited&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;like a hero in the night skyscraper&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to take that leap of faith&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and become greater&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;maybe soulmates aren’t found&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but are created&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it was worth the pain and the waiting&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know we’re scared&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you’ve promised that you’ll never hurt me&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and never abandon or flee&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as I promised that I’ll still love you&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;even if we get old&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;long distance as of this moment&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but I still wanna wrap my arms around you&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and hold&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we maybe physically far&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but so energetically close&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;time don’t exist when I talk to you&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the clocks become completely froze&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a new story is about to be told&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry that you were cheated&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as my previous attempts of love&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;were untreated&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as everything happens for a reason,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;canon events,&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;makes us grow and ascend&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as you are my Mary Jane and Gwen&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;at the same time&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but you are yourself&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;which I love the most&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know we’re not perfect&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but no one is&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;your the reason why&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I keep pushing and&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;why life is so beautiful to live&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I see why now&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this love is so unbound&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>MoonBin K-pop Star Dead Gematria Decoded</title>
        <published>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/">&lt;p&gt;The days between Kim Jong-hyun death to moon bin his exactly 74 months apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like how 47 the reflection of 74 as Suicide = 47&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moon bin = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ritual Sacrifice = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concert Moonbin was supposed to attend called Dream Concert equals to 56 and 205 as he died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The record label that Astro is with Fatagio equates to 44 like kill = 44 in gematria and how he died on a Wednesday equating to 44 in the same Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asian also equates to 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kpop idol = 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kpop group Astro equates to 19, as he died on the 19th of April as Moonbin and Astro also equating to 35 in Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the Moon cycle is every 19 years&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chaos = 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19 hijackers in 9&#x2F;11 to Covid-19 in 2019&#x2F;early 2020&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and even Kpop star = 35 and 46 as well with sacrifice = 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And 4&#x2F;19&#x2F;23 has a date numerology of 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From his last birthday 1&#x2F;26&#x2F;23 to his death is exactly 83 days, as Murder = 83 and so is Seoul South Korea = 83. Also to note he died on the anniversary of the movie Murder by Numbers&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also noticed that the Astro logo looks like the Star of David&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;what clues they are trying to hint at is something related to space and astrology, with his name being Moonbin&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TST Yohan death to Moonbin is 44 weeks apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli and Moonbin both have the gematria of 35&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also equates to 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His death occurred during Space X ship exploding, with the theme revolving around space, the moon, astrology, etc.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Astro color scheme is purple as Prince color was purple as this occurred very closely to Prince death&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>How Hip-Hop became my Threapy</title>
        <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*Exdv8YZ-61wvNOekU9DPHg.png&quot; alt=&quot;hiphopimage&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me. This lead me to the point of finding a healthy outlet and some ways to face my shadows within me that I was dealing with that were brought up during these events with her. During our separation, I found that I loved making music and making my own lyrics on how I felt with everything that was happening in my personal life. There were always just notes on my phone and never really tried to rap or anything, until around later that year, where I made two rap songs. After always being inspired by the world of rapping, poetry, etc. I finally took action on what I wanted to do for a while since the beginning of that year. In 2021, I still had those wounds on what happened as I never really listened to songs that resonated on how I felt since, I didn’t wanted to feel negative. I realized that this was an act of spiritual bypassing as I didn’t want to acknowledge myself truly and as a person who both have light and dark aspects, which we all have. I particularly dived in more into the world of Hip-Hop, finding new artists, songs, sub-genre, style, etc. with the subject matter of vulnerability and heartbreak. Albums and songs that I listened to, that got me through those times and still is to this day. A sense of a feeling that shows how Hip-Hop evolved so much to express one self. With Hip-Hop&#x2F;Rap as well being a mostly masculine trait, it shows how it is to be a man and at the same time not shunning those inner feelings within us and vent it in a way of an art form. You could see this within rap artist Kayne West, who revolutionized of showing ones emotions within the world of Hip-Hop with his album, 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak rather just Hip-Hop on the topic just gangsters, money, sex and drugs all the time, and open the doors to everyone to rap no matter where they come from and don’t have to be a certain way to always act tough, aggressive, violent, they can be comfortable within their own skins. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=J_CT8dy2mlc&amp;t=766s&quot;&gt; &lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;The Impact of 808s &amp; Heartbreaks&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a therapist costing a lot, and my own self therapy by reflection, learning psychology and the shadow self while listening to Hip-Hop music the tackles vulnerable topics that I can deeply relate to and a sense that I’m not alone on what I’m going through. After this, it got me inspired to make more of my own music, lyrics and full expression without judgement along with freestyling, which really feels like another way for me to meditate and a sense of being very spiritual as rapping, deals with one of the higher chakras, the throat chakra as you get this spiritual bliss while doing it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some recommended albums that helped me through during my separation:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brockhampton — Ginger &#x2F; RoadRunner: New Lights, New Machine &#x2F; Saturation &#x2F; Saturation II &#x2F; Saturation III&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadeca — From Me to You &#x2F; From Me to You (Deluxe)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayne West — KIDS SEE GHOSTS &#x2F; 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak &#x2F; My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jaden — SYRE &#x2F; ERYS &#x2F; The Sunset Tapes: A Cool Tape Story&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Cole — 4 Your Eyez Only &#x2F; Born Sinner&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joey Bada$$ — 2000&#x2F;1999&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Koi — before it’s too late&#x2F; 10&amp;amp;2&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Brian — The Sailor&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse(Soundtrack From &amp;amp; Inspired by the Motion Picture)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than that, check out my music on&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;open.spotify.com&#x2F;artist&#x2F;1ojpTukPyY4MaB7tseXdtQ&quot;&gt; Spotify,&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.soundcloud.com&#x2F;PhantomBroken&quot;&gt;SoundCloud&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;@PhantomBroken&quot;&gt; YouTube&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; that I’m making and support it if you like it! Also starting a movement with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;peterparkercode.github.io&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hip-hop-and-threapy&#x2F;.&#x2F;clga&quot;&gt;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; instead of the parental advisory logo and wanting Hip-Hop music to go against the agendas that’s been going on in this world&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*xGdyYyKGfdOAQPBjXu1AMw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gcjU-7dLV_HT0vkWqnI8cA.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY sticker&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Down the image to add to your song art covers!&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*VV-VB3jGenl_oBkuFqxPDw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CLGA&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Flipping the Script (Cobra Kai Philosophy)</title>
        <published>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=yZFBtHG3okI&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*FwO48aT4QmUIQmZj9lMPmQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;ying yang&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;The balance between Miyagi Do (feminine) and Cobra Kai (masculine)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This show signal handily helped me so much when going through life. Throughout this show, we see Eli who was an introvert, hated himself, and was constantly bullied by his appearance with his cleft lip until he took the tough love advice from Johnny Lawrence and grabbed life by the balls and turning the tables that he has the power, while not waiting for anyone to make a change for himself.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You see that… Doesn’t matter if you’re a loser, or a nerd, or a freak… all that matters is that you become BADASS!” — Johnny Lawrence&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does it really mean to “Flip the Script”?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, I see it as looking at your strengths instead of the weakness we may pay attention too much, which leads to self doubt, fears, and self-fulfilling prophecy. Acknowledge the weakness, and use that to your advantage. So face that dragon whatever it maybe (ie. taking action towards that girl you like, in a fight or competition, etc.) while going in with it that the script that life give us you may see as a disadvantage, though now looking at it with a different perspective and lenses to now it’s your advantage.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=RO6GPt6xbv8&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 3 (2021)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Willing to fight smart whether its an opponent, or the adversity through life.
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=https:&#x2F;&#x2F;youtu.be&#x2F;haRKrSfKVg0?feature=shared&amp;t=42&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me let you in a little secret. It’s not just the haircut, or the back tattoo, it’s the way of life man. You just gotta feel the energy and live in the moment.” — Eli Moskowitz aka Hawk&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hawk himself doesn’t realize he is applying the philosophy with yang of flowing, being able to move freely physically and mentally, while we see Demetri acting stiff and awkward. He is in the flow state, like what Bruce Lee meant while being like water.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kxZZlk1mK0VBKX88lDuU-g.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If I want to punch, I’m gonna do it man” — Bruce Lee&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water is never stiff, it moves and flows without any judgement or second thoughts to do said things. It adapts to it’s environment while being one with it, without the conscious thinking of doubt that we usually do. When you try to punch or hurt water, it doesn’t react and instead embodies the hit. While it being the most softest element, at the same time, it can penetrate a rock or slice through metal. And the fact that we are 70% made up of water as well. Water is liquid consciousness. I think this philosophy and the things that are taught in the Tao, is more towards, Miyagi Do’s ways of teaching compared to Cobra Kai’s “Strike first, strike hard.” mentality, balance of these two is needed. Like Bruce Lee said, wanting to strike a punch (Cobra Kai’s philosophy) while being comfortable in one own skin, with no judgment (Miyagi Do’s philosophy), this is what Hawk does while being at the party and will also learn more of later on in Season 4.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another character Demetri, who is best friends of Hawk, has the same trouble of standing up for himself, self doubt, and self fulfilling prophecies that turns against him. Instead of him going to Cobra Kai like Hawk did, he went to Miyagi Do where he did seek the same aspects and philosophy though in a way of a balance and self inner peace. His development overtime happened slow and gradually compared to Hawk’s transformation through within Season 3, he as well “Flipped the Script”.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=Z919pABSkQo&amp;t=1161s&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Demetri&#x27;s ark&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
In the video, Demetri’s Dating Advice (Cobra Kai Analysis) by Watch Party, I think we can all relate with our brain power and imagination taking the control in situations where we may find it out of our comfort zone. Overtime, in the series, Demetri uses his brain power and imagination, as the upper hand while putting self beliefs that changes his script in life for the good. And he “Flipped the Script” towards the girl he liked, Yasmine, to get her interested within him by unconsciously planting the seed by her writing it down. (Kinda like Inception)
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kiORtWdH6Hr3TcdA5Q5pVQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;yasmine&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
Life is all about perspective. So apply “Flipping the Script” into your own life in each creative way, as long it is with good intent and is uplifting yourself and others to be greater. “With great power, comes great responsibility” — Uncle Ben.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gRbe5RRCfy3xxc2gzaj6ZQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee Quotes&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;You are your own self fulgilling prophecy&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Welp, that’s my take on it, and while your at it, go learn a martial arts if you haven’t already to grasp this concept even more. Until then, don’t stop being a badass.
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>We Always Have a Choice</title>
        <published>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*e74uJ-7Th6ow9m3ZXu9pTA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 1&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Source:Ultimate Spider-Man Comic&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*D1h9p9Xvdd8W73hxUiddGg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 2&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*T9OeDOH5Bq8tT-PGNCMQEg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 3&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With great power, there must also come — great responsibility.” No matter what in life, we always have a choice to make the right decisions, even if it feels like we’re forced to do said things that doesn’t resonate with us and know that is not the best option. We have the choice to not only to make the right decisions for ourselves, but for others and for the sake of the betterment of humanity. With so many things that happened these past years of shambles not only in our personal lives, though the whole world needing to heal. We all have that power within us to change for the good. I also think the reason why till this day, I still love Spider-Man, is that the more I get older, the lessons within those stories that I read, watch, or play, makes more sense to me. Peter Parker, someone who took his powers for granted, using it in ways of for his own gain and not for the people around him as he had the choice to stop that robber, though didn’t, which led to the death of Uncle Ben. With every choice we make, comes with a certain strength and power. Only thing is, how would we use it?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*HDp005Id05BSXeqXRwLSrw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 3&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Reunited</title>
        <published>2022-02-08T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-02-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/reunited/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/reunited/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/reunited/">&lt;p&gt;this tension is building up inside of me&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to the point where I don’t know how to explain it within me&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;something about us sparked a flame that I would never forget&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;too bad we never commit, I think deep down is what we regret&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just wanna hug you tight&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;fight for you right by your side&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;close off the outside world&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as we run in the beautiful night&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;looking into your eyes got me hypnotize&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;reminiscing about that smile of yours&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it had some type of style&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel this energy that is bittersweet&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it tingles in my chest&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;someday I cannot rest&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thinking about this pain of our separation&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;why we never open up&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we put up a facade that we’re doing okay&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but deep down we’re hurt&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;sometimes it feels like that the memories we had fade&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;though this thing that we have will never go away&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my intuition I know you still think about me by the days&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanna own up to my mistakes and forgive you and myself&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;because I know this connection we had was a crazy experience that we felt&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;like how you melt the insides of me as I blush and cry on how things ended&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but this isn’t over as a new chapter has ascended and soon enough we will&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;reunite as expected…&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Illusion of Money</title>
        <published>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;64.media.tumblr.com&amp;#x2F;0bf13392b5490986fc25c8912c2f39b6&amp;#x2F;tumblr_n04yhjlXRr1tqg1b3o1_500.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;They Live&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more I reflect, thinking deep about it ever since this whole world changed, I’m now questioning within this system’s ego, my ego, and everyone elses. I see pass through it now, the way this world conditioned us within a tradition, something that the system raise and taught us to do since begining of schooling, which is to make money. But why though? The one thing out of everythung within this system that is keeping us stuck here, staying comfortable and not fight for whats going on in this Matrix. If you see pass it, money doesn’t exist, its the maya, an illusion that decieve us. We give it power and it distracts us, as it fuels this system. Question this to yourself, how come throughout our life, we never seen in public or outside in nature most of the times, something simple like a tree that grows fruits that you could pick, or a public gardan of vegetables that you can get and take it home with you to eat? Sounds logical that we should encounter these things as it was from mother nature. But no, its all behind a pay wall, cut off for people who needs it the most, how can the world be starving right now, if we can simply grow crops? Oh, but this inoculation is “free” for everyone to take, get free donuts, burgers, fries, alcohol, etc. But not free resources that mother nature gave us and is good for our health??? We are living in a backwards world. Everything we do within the system is backwards. And if you see it transparent even more, its crazy how anyone could make something right now, and get the whole world to value that, even if that thing in reality is nothing. Like a piece of paper, we get condition to think we should spend lifetime to get it. I mean look at crypto, its an illusion as well, just a number on a screen and we value that and chase a currency that you can’t even see. Why? Because we give it the power for it to survive like any illusion. Its an endless cycle that we gotta break. Like “In this world nothing can be said to be certain, except death and taxes.” , how THE FUCK THEY GOT US THINKING LIKE THAT when these elites built this matrix?!?!!?! WE NEED TO GET THEM OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW AND WE CAN!!! If everyone stopped participating in their game, everybody stopped paying taxes, to these criminals, that would be one step for humanity. And always hear “well how am I supposed to put food on the table without money?” THIS IS NOT THE WAY WE SUPPOSED TO BE LIVING IN THE FIRST PLACE! Well, I don’t know, how about all the free food from nature that we can eat right now, but they blocked it off. We aren’t independent at all, from our grandparents generation, being independent with EVERYTHING, like farms, foods that hasn’t been posioned, purified water, a COMMUNITY that WORKED TOGETHER, thats REAL value right there. How did we ended up like this where everything is corporate like Monsanto, blocked off needs that is already free within nature from the public. We gotta start thinking forwadly and find a way to come together before its too late. As we are still in the system and “need” money as it was designed this system, for now, I guess we gotta do what we do until that time comes and come together as a conscious which I hope it will. These agendas are not stopping and we will be left with no choice but to end they’re illusion that they’ve blinded us with. Stay strong… 🧠&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.giphy.com%2Fmedia%2FzXmbOaTpbY6mA%2Fgiphy.gif&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=9415215e96e1ed7d453ddde195b7f7118a07ca5f6bedbbba6269a4959c9f7329&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;Matrix Code&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Moving Foward, Heartbreak and Healing</title>
        <published>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/">&lt;p&gt;I keep running away from the things that I need to face, being attached on with the past and I can’t run and hide forever. Made a lot of mistakes with that connection that could’ve been something but it wasn’t mean’t to be. I’m still learning on how to move forward from it, which is still a challenge for me, reminsing about the times I had with her, mourning on what I lost. Though is it something that I really lost or that experince has already served its purpose and I returned it. That experince which had a lesson that I had to learn and still learning from. Theres things that is not in our control and others are in control. Its like a handful of cards that God, a higher power, universe etc. Gave us in life, that we have to accept, with the inevitable. Things don’t last forever family, friends, relationships all soon will have to come to an end at one point or another. The people in our lives and the foundation we build with them will soon, not have purpose anymore. Everything has purpose and we will have to move forward, return it and look towards a new sets of lessons in life that will have a new type of purpose. People change, the world is changing, and I have to come to accpetance that aye, she and I have, changed and even if it feels like we don’t know eachother anymore though thats life. And that makes me go into a deeper question, did I liked her for her, or the idea of her 🤔 when it comes to my acceptance to what reailty is and not the fantasy and the things that are now the past&#x2F;memories? What is it that I can’t accept and move on from? Everything happens for a reason, I don’t believe in things being a “coincidence” and whoever made that word, must’ve been too much of a rational and logical minded person, I wouldn’t like to hang out with 😂. Everything down with synchronicities, angel numbers, you thinking about something and that thing pops up, going through a bad day and some good karma comes to you, can’t be a coincdence. This “lost” of a connection could be a blessing in disguise that I am not seeing? Is me holding on to that branch of the past and not letting go of it, blocking those blessings? Who knows until you actually let go of that branch.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Divde and Conquer by the Elites. FREE YOUR MIND | WHEN WILL WE COME TOGETHER?</title>
        <published>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FOBwuHLkqgKM%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=b34b3cb2d46e67c01fc0007f26baf1e2a7d4fe8620b67e523575b40f2f71b8cd&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;civil war&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew I couldn’t kill them. More powerful men than me have tried. But if I could get them to kill eachother…” - Zemo.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SEE THROUGH THE ILLUSION AND THE AGENDA THAT IS BEING WAGED ON US. All of these hate crimes on the news and mainstream is to DIVIDE AND CONQUER US. They dont want us coming TOGETHER as a community and putting our differences to the side! If that were to happen, we’ll be too powerful than these higher ups and puppet on a string! They got us FIGHTING EACH OTHER instead of us fighting these “elites” whos doing this to us in the first place! See the repeated tactics they use against us. 9&#x2F;11, racially divide and hate towards Musilms creating a false flag to put us in control. Now with this pandemic, racial division again towards the black community, get us rally up, go against our neighbor, killing each other. Now more false flags on Asians and creating illusions by the media. We already know who is responsible for this whole “pandemic” in the first place! Research Event 201, these cover boys like Bill Gates, Fauci, Joe Biden, Trump etc. Is being controlled by the numbers, rituals, etc.! Hint: all roads lead to Rome. Like how in Captain America Civil War, the spilt of the Avengers was detrimental and came with consequences of that spilt. Fighting each other instead of looking at whos behind the scenes pulling the strings! They DON’T WANT US COMING TOGETHER! IF WE DO ITS OVER FOR THEM! THEY DEPEND ON US! WE HAVE THE POWER! Why you think they enslaved us? GovernMENT! Govern the MENTAL, THE MIND 🧠. This is a phycological warfare that their doing on us! KNOW THAT YOU HAVE THE POWER! Don’t fight your neighbor. He’s not the enemy. #FreeYourMind&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Personal journal</title>
        <published>2019-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2019-10-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/journal/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/journal/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/journal/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;2024-02-08&quot;&gt;2024-02-08&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Updating this website and adding more things to it! So far it looks really amazing and giving me so many nostalgic feelings about the old internet. One thing I do want to add on this site is a music player which is something I’ll have to figure out in the mean time, though so far I’m liking it!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
