<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - Matrix</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/matrix/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/matrix/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Going through the Dark Night of The Soul. Why is this Happening?</title>
        <published>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/">&lt;p&gt;Going through the Dark Night of the Soul, can sometimes feel pretty scary… the way that we’ve perceived life is crumbling before our eyes. Everything from what we believed is to be to being revealed what the truth is either in our personal lives or looking what society is. All of these multiple factors were the reason why the Dark Night of the Soul happened to me. But why does this happen in the first place anyways? Is it because of those external factors that we may think is the reason why it’s all happening and blame the outside, or is it because that we chose to experience this in order to grow? When researching this topic and coming to that conclusion that I, myself either unconsciously or consciously chose to go through this in order to get rid of the beliefs that didn’t serve me. Which made all the sense to me, because I chose the path of questioning myself, reality and this world. I consciously chose to pursue spirituality and self development to connect with myself even more. Which the outcome of this was a feeling of being born again, spiritual bliss and life was amplified even more. It was like I put on a pair of lenses that made me see life as this beautiful thing, from the trees, to the animals, the connection I’ve had and what not. But, this comes with the price of needing to know what the truth of this world or Matrix is. From seeing what the knowledge you’ve gained as a gift, to now looking at it as a curse. When 2020 happened, that’s when I had to face the reality and consciously decided to look into “conspiracies”, who was behind the pandemic, wars, killings and things that have been enslaving humanity for centuries. With me wanting to know the truth and refusing the pretty lies, I’ve gotten what I’ve want. Thus the way I’ve conveyed on what reality is as a kid, having to question even more on the matter, I realize it is a necessary part on one’s spiritual path and self development. Along with other factors taking place like separation I had from my friends because of lockdowns and not aligning with them anymore, as I’ve questioned the very things that is hard to come to terms with, but it’s needed. But most importantly being in separation from the girl that I’ve liked from the time, trying to reach out to keep our connection alive as the result was her admitting to avoided me, ghosting, running away and feelings of unrequited love, even though I still felt her presence when we weren’t talking at that time. All these factors, made me realize that I was in the Dark Night of the Soul. All I can say is to be patient on whatever you may have to face that you’ve may have been unconsciously running your whole life or seeing things not being the same anymore. That’s what I most importantly feel but I promise, that things will get better, even if it seems bleak, keeping facing that feeling of hopelessness, heartbreak, fears etc. and integrating that shadow. Realize that you were and always are a complete whole being, this too shall past. Be self forgiving and have self patience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>MoonBin K-pop Star Dead Gematria Decoded</title>
        <published>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/">&lt;p&gt;The days between Kim Jong-hyun death to moon bin his exactly 74 months apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like how 47 the reflection of 74 as Suicide = 47&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moon bin = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ritual Sacrifice = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concert Moonbin was supposed to attend called Dream Concert equals to 56 and 205 as he died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The record label that Astro is with Fatagio equates to 44 like kill = 44 in gematria and how he died on a Wednesday equating to 44 in the same Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asian also equates to 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kpop idol = 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kpop group Astro equates to 19, as he died on the 19th of April as Moonbin and Astro also equating to 35 in Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the Moon cycle is every 19 years&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chaos = 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19 hijackers in 9&#x2F;11 to Covid-19 in 2019&#x2F;early 2020&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and even Kpop star = 35 and 46 as well with sacrifice = 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And 4&#x2F;19&#x2F;23 has a date numerology of 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From his last birthday 1&#x2F;26&#x2F;23 to his death is exactly 83 days, as Murder = 83 and so is Seoul South Korea = 83. Also to note he died on the anniversary of the movie Murder by Numbers&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also noticed that the Astro logo looks like the Star of David&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;what clues they are trying to hint at is something related to space and astrology, with his name being Moonbin&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TST Yohan death to Moonbin is 44 weeks apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli and Moonbin both have the gematria of 35&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also equates to 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His death occurred during Space X ship exploding, with the theme revolving around space, the moon, astrology, etc.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Astro color scheme is purple as Prince color was purple as this occurred very closely to Prince death&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Illusion of Money</title>
        <published>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-08-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-21-08-illusion-of-money/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;64.media.tumblr.com&amp;#x2F;0bf13392b5490986fc25c8912c2f39b6&amp;#x2F;tumblr_n04yhjlXRr1tqg1b3o1_500.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;They Live&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more I reflect, thinking deep about it ever since this whole world changed, I’m now questioning within this system’s ego, my ego, and everyone elses. I see pass through it now, the way this world conditioned us within a tradition, something that the system raise and taught us to do since begining of schooling, which is to make money. But why though? The one thing out of everythung within this system that is keeping us stuck here, staying comfortable and not fight for whats going on in this Matrix. If you see pass it, money doesn’t exist, its the maya, an illusion that decieve us. We give it power and it distracts us, as it fuels this system. Question this to yourself, how come throughout our life, we never seen in public or outside in nature most of the times, something simple like a tree that grows fruits that you could pick, or a public gardan of vegetables that you can get and take it home with you to eat? Sounds logical that we should encounter these things as it was from mother nature. But no, its all behind a pay wall, cut off for people who needs it the most, how can the world be starving right now, if we can simply grow crops? Oh, but this inoculation is “free” for everyone to take, get free donuts, burgers, fries, alcohol, etc. But not free resources that mother nature gave us and is good for our health??? We are living in a backwards world. Everything we do within the system is backwards. And if you see it transparent even more, its crazy how anyone could make something right now, and get the whole world to value that, even if that thing in reality is nothing. Like a piece of paper, we get condition to think we should spend lifetime to get it. I mean look at crypto, its an illusion as well, just a number on a screen and we value that and chase a currency that you can’t even see. Why? Because we give it the power for it to survive like any illusion. Its an endless cycle that we gotta break. Like “In this world nothing can be said to be certain, except death and taxes.” , how THE FUCK THEY GOT US THINKING LIKE THAT when these elites built this matrix?!?!!?! WE NEED TO GET THEM OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW AND WE CAN!!! If everyone stopped participating in their game, everybody stopped paying taxes, to these criminals, that would be one step for humanity. And always hear “well how am I supposed to put food on the table without money?” THIS IS NOT THE WAY WE SUPPOSED TO BE LIVING IN THE FIRST PLACE! Well, I don’t know, how about all the free food from nature that we can eat right now, but they blocked it off. We aren’t independent at all, from our grandparents generation, being independent with EVERYTHING, like farms, foods that hasn’t been posioned, purified water, a COMMUNITY that WORKED TOGETHER, thats REAL value right there. How did we ended up like this where everything is corporate like Monsanto, blocked off needs that is already free within nature from the public. We gotta start thinking forwadly and find a way to come together before its too late. As we are still in the system and “need” money as it was designed this system, for now, I guess we gotta do what we do until that time comes and come together as a conscious which I hope it will. These agendas are not stopping and we will be left with no choice but to end they’re illusion that they’ve blinded us with. Stay strong… 🧠&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.giphy.com%2Fmedia%2FzXmbOaTpbY6mA%2Fgiphy.gif&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=9415215e96e1ed7d453ddde195b7f7118a07ca5f6bedbbba6269a4959c9f7329&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;Matrix Code&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Divde and Conquer by the Elites. FREE YOUR MIND | WHEN WILL WE COME TOGETHER?</title>
        <published>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FOBwuHLkqgKM%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=b34b3cb2d46e67c01fc0007f26baf1e2a7d4fe8620b67e523575b40f2f71b8cd&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;civil war&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew I couldn’t kill them. More powerful men than me have tried. But if I could get them to kill eachother…” - Zemo.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SEE THROUGH THE ILLUSION AND THE AGENDA THAT IS BEING WAGED ON US. All of these hate crimes on the news and mainstream is to DIVIDE AND CONQUER US. They dont want us coming TOGETHER as a community and putting our differences to the side! If that were to happen, we’ll be too powerful than these higher ups and puppet on a string! They got us FIGHTING EACH OTHER instead of us fighting these “elites” whos doing this to us in the first place! See the repeated tactics they use against us. 9&#x2F;11, racially divide and hate towards Musilms creating a false flag to put us in control. Now with this pandemic, racial division again towards the black community, get us rally up, go against our neighbor, killing each other. Now more false flags on Asians and creating illusions by the media. We already know who is responsible for this whole “pandemic” in the first place! Research Event 201, these cover boys like Bill Gates, Fauci, Joe Biden, Trump etc. Is being controlled by the numbers, rituals, etc.! Hint: all roads lead to Rome. Like how in Captain America Civil War, the spilt of the Avengers was detrimental and came with consequences of that spilt. Fighting each other instead of looking at whos behind the scenes pulling the strings! They DON’T WANT US COMING TOGETHER! IF WE DO ITS OVER FOR THEM! THEY DEPEND ON US! WE HAVE THE POWER! Why you think they enslaved us? GovernMENT! Govern the MENTAL, THE MIND 🧠. This is a phycological warfare that their doing on us! KNOW THAT YOU HAVE THE POWER! Don’t fight your neighbor. He’s not the enemy. #FreeYourMind&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
