<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - IG Archives</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/ig-archives/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/ig-archives/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Moving Foward, Heartbreak and Healing</title>
        <published>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/">&lt;p&gt;I keep running away from the things that I need to face, being attached on with the past and I can’t run and hide forever. Made a lot of mistakes with that connection that could’ve been something but it wasn’t mean’t to be. I’m still learning on how to move forward from it, which is still a challenge for me, reminsing about the times I had with her, mourning on what I lost. Though is it something that I really lost or that experince has already served its purpose and I returned it. That experince which had a lesson that I had to learn and still learning from. Theres things that is not in our control and others are in control. Its like a handful of cards that God, a higher power, universe etc. Gave us in life, that we have to accept, with the inevitable. Things don’t last forever family, friends, relationships all soon will have to come to an end at one point or another. The people in our lives and the foundation we build with them will soon, not have purpose anymore. Everything has purpose and we will have to move forward, return it and look towards a new sets of lessons in life that will have a new type of purpose. People change, the world is changing, and I have to come to accpetance that aye, she and I have, changed and even if it feels like we don’t know eachother anymore though thats life. And that makes me go into a deeper question, did I liked her for her, or the idea of her 🤔 when it comes to my acceptance to what reailty is and not the fantasy and the things that are now the past&#x2F;memories? What is it that I can’t accept and move on from? Everything happens for a reason, I don’t believe in things being a “coincidence” and whoever made that word, must’ve been too much of a rational and logical minded person, I wouldn’t like to hang out with 😂. Everything down with synchronicities, angel numbers, you thinking about something and that thing pops up, going through a bad day and some good karma comes to you, can’t be a coincdence. This “lost” of a connection could be a blessing in disguise that I am not seeing? Is me holding on to that branch of the past and not letting go of it, blocking those blessings? Who knows until you actually let go of that branch.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Divde and Conquer by the Elites. FREE YOUR MIND | WHEN WILL WE COME TOGETHER?</title>
        <published>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FOBwuHLkqgKM%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=b34b3cb2d46e67c01fc0007f26baf1e2a7d4fe8620b67e523575b40f2f71b8cd&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;civil war&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew I couldn’t kill them. More powerful men than me have tried. But if I could get them to kill eachother…” - Zemo.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SEE THROUGH THE ILLUSION AND THE AGENDA THAT IS BEING WAGED ON US. All of these hate crimes on the news and mainstream is to DIVIDE AND CONQUER US. They dont want us coming TOGETHER as a community and putting our differences to the side! If that were to happen, we’ll be too powerful than these higher ups and puppet on a string! They got us FIGHTING EACH OTHER instead of us fighting these “elites” whos doing this to us in the first place! See the repeated tactics they use against us. 9&#x2F;11, racially divide and hate towards Musilms creating a false flag to put us in control. Now with this pandemic, racial division again towards the black community, get us rally up, go against our neighbor, killing each other. Now more false flags on Asians and creating illusions by the media. We already know who is responsible for this whole “pandemic” in the first place! Research Event 201, these cover boys like Bill Gates, Fauci, Joe Biden, Trump etc. Is being controlled by the numbers, rituals, etc.! Hint: all roads lead to Rome. Like how in Captain America Civil War, the spilt of the Avengers was detrimental and came with consequences of that spilt. Fighting each other instead of looking at whos behind the scenes pulling the strings! They DON’T WANT US COMING TOGETHER! IF WE DO ITS OVER FOR THEM! THEY DEPEND ON US! WE HAVE THE POWER! Why you think they enslaved us? GovernMENT! Govern the MENTAL, THE MIND 🧠. This is a phycological warfare that their doing on us! KNOW THAT YOU HAVE THE POWER! Don’t fight your neighbor. He’s not the enemy. #FreeYourMind&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
