<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - Soulmates</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/soulmates/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/soulmates/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Going through the Dark Night of The Soul. Why is this Happening?</title>
        <published>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/dark-night-of-soul/">&lt;p&gt;Going through the Dark Night of the Soul, can sometimes feel pretty scary… the way that we’ve perceived life is crumbling before our eyes. Everything from what we believed is to be to being revealed what the truth is either in our personal lives or looking what society is. All of these multiple factors were the reason why the Dark Night of the Soul happened to me. But why does this happen in the first place anyways? Is it because of those external factors that we may think is the reason why it’s all happening and blame the outside, or is it because that we chose to experience this in order to grow? When researching this topic and coming to that conclusion that I, myself either unconsciously or consciously chose to go through this in order to get rid of the beliefs that didn’t serve me. Which made all the sense to me, because I chose the path of questioning myself, reality and this world. I consciously chose to pursue spirituality and self development to connect with myself even more. Which the outcome of this was a feeling of being born again, spiritual bliss and life was amplified even more. It was like I put on a pair of lenses that made me see life as this beautiful thing, from the trees, to the animals, the connection I’ve had and what not. But, this comes with the price of needing to know what the truth of this world or Matrix is. From seeing what the knowledge you’ve gained as a gift, to now looking at it as a curse. When 2020 happened, that’s when I had to face the reality and consciously decided to look into “conspiracies”, who was behind the pandemic, wars, killings and things that have been enslaving humanity for centuries. With me wanting to know the truth and refusing the pretty lies, I’ve gotten what I’ve want. Thus the way I’ve conveyed on what reality is as a kid, having to question even more on the matter, I realize it is a necessary part on one’s spiritual path and self development. Along with other factors taking place like separation I had from my friends because of lockdowns and not aligning with them anymore, as I’ve questioned the very things that is hard to come to terms with, but it’s needed. But most importantly being in separation from the girl that I’ve liked from the time, trying to reach out to keep our connection alive as the result was her admitting to avoided me, ghosting, running away and feelings of unrequited love, even though I still felt her presence when we weren’t talking at that time. All these factors, made me realize that I was in the Dark Night of the Soul. All I can say is to be patient on whatever you may have to face that you’ve may have been unconsciously running your whole life or seeing things not being the same anymore. That’s what I most importantly feel but I promise, that things will get better, even if it seems bleak, keeping facing that feeling of hopelessness, heartbreak, fears etc. and integrating that shadow. Realize that you were and always are a complete whole being, this too shall past. Be self forgiving and have self patience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>How Hip-Hop became my Threapy</title>
        <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*Exdv8YZ-61wvNOekU9DPHg.png&quot; alt=&quot;hiphopimage&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me. This lead me to the point of finding a healthy outlet and some ways to face my shadows within me that I was dealing with that were brought up during these events with her. During our separation, I found that I loved making music and making my own lyrics on how I felt with everything that was happening in my personal life. There were always just notes on my phone and never really tried to rap or anything, until around later that year, where I made two rap songs. After always being inspired by the world of rapping, poetry, etc. I finally took action on what I wanted to do for a while since the beginning of that year. In 2021, I still had those wounds on what happened as I never really listened to songs that resonated on how I felt since, I didn’t wanted to feel negative. I realized that this was an act of spiritual bypassing as I didn’t want to acknowledge myself truly and as a person who both have light and dark aspects, which we all have. I particularly dived in more into the world of Hip-Hop, finding new artists, songs, sub-genre, style, etc. with the subject matter of vulnerability and heartbreak. Albums and songs that I listened to, that got me through those times and still is to this day. A sense of a feeling that shows how Hip-Hop evolved so much to express one self. With Hip-Hop&#x2F;Rap as well being a mostly masculine trait, it shows how it is to be a man and at the same time not shunning those inner feelings within us and vent it in a way of an art form. You could see this within rap artist Kayne West, who revolutionized of showing ones emotions within the world of Hip-Hop with his album, 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak rather just Hip-Hop on the topic just gangsters, money, sex and drugs all the time, and open the doors to everyone to rap no matter where they come from and don’t have to be a certain way to always act tough, aggressive, violent, they can be comfortable within their own skins. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=J_CT8dy2mlc&amp;t=766s&quot;&gt; &lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;The Impact of 808s &amp; Heartbreaks&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a therapist costing a lot, and my own self therapy by reflection, learning psychology and the shadow self while listening to Hip-Hop music the tackles vulnerable topics that I can deeply relate to and a sense that I’m not alone on what I’m going through. After this, it got me inspired to make more of my own music, lyrics and full expression without judgement along with freestyling, which really feels like another way for me to meditate and a sense of being very spiritual as rapping, deals with one of the higher chakras, the throat chakra as you get this spiritual bliss while doing it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some recommended albums that helped me through during my separation:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brockhampton — Ginger &#x2F; RoadRunner: New Lights, New Machine &#x2F; Saturation &#x2F; Saturation II &#x2F; Saturation III&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadeca — From Me to You &#x2F; From Me to You (Deluxe)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayne West — KIDS SEE GHOSTS &#x2F; 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak &#x2F; My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jaden — SYRE &#x2F; ERYS &#x2F; The Sunset Tapes: A Cool Tape Story&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Cole — 4 Your Eyez Only &#x2F; Born Sinner&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joey Bada$$ — 2000&#x2F;1999&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Koi — before it’s too late&#x2F; 10&amp;amp;2&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Brian — The Sailor&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse(Soundtrack From &amp;amp; Inspired by the Motion Picture)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than that, check out my music on&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;open.spotify.com&#x2F;artist&#x2F;1ojpTukPyY4MaB7tseXdtQ&quot;&gt; Spotify,&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.soundcloud.com&#x2F;PhantomBroken&quot;&gt;SoundCloud&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;@PhantomBroken&quot;&gt; YouTube&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; that I’m making and support it if you like it! Also starting a movement with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;peterparkercode.github.io&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hip-hop-and-threapy&#x2F;.&#x2F;clga&quot;&gt;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; instead of the parental advisory logo and wanting Hip-Hop music to go against the agendas that’s been going on in this world&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*xGdyYyKGfdOAQPBjXu1AMw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gcjU-7dLV_HT0vkWqnI8cA.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY sticker&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Down the image to add to your song art covers!&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*VV-VB3jGenl_oBkuFqxPDw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CLGA&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Moving Foward, Heartbreak and Healing</title>
        <published>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-04-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2021-25-04-heartbreak/">&lt;p&gt;I keep running away from the things that I need to face, being attached on with the past and I can’t run and hide forever. Made a lot of mistakes with that connection that could’ve been something but it wasn’t mean’t to be. I’m still learning on how to move forward from it, which is still a challenge for me, reminsing about the times I had with her, mourning on what I lost. Though is it something that I really lost or that experince has already served its purpose and I returned it. That experince which had a lesson that I had to learn and still learning from. Theres things that is not in our control and others are in control. Its like a handful of cards that God, a higher power, universe etc. Gave us in life, that we have to accept, with the inevitable. Things don’t last forever family, friends, relationships all soon will have to come to an end at one point or another. The people in our lives and the foundation we build with them will soon, not have purpose anymore. Everything has purpose and we will have to move forward, return it and look towards a new sets of lessons in life that will have a new type of purpose. People change, the world is changing, and I have to come to accpetance that aye, she and I have, changed and even if it feels like we don’t know eachother anymore though thats life. And that makes me go into a deeper question, did I liked her for her, or the idea of her 🤔 when it comes to my acceptance to what reailty is and not the fantasy and the things that are now the past&#x2F;memories? What is it that I can’t accept and move on from? Everything happens for a reason, I don’t believe in things being a “coincidence” and whoever made that word, must’ve been too much of a rational and logical minded person, I wouldn’t like to hang out with 😂. Everything down with synchronicities, angel numbers, you thinking about something and that thing pops up, going through a bad day and some good karma comes to you, can’t be a coincdence. This “lost” of a connection could be a blessing in disguise that I am not seeing? Is me holding on to that branch of the past and not letting go of it, blocking those blessings? Who knows until you actually let go of that branch.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
