<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - movies</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/movies/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/movies/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Flipping the Script (Cobra Kai Philosophy)</title>
        <published>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=yZFBtHG3okI&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*FwO48aT4QmUIQmZj9lMPmQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;ying yang&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;The balance between Miyagi Do (feminine) and Cobra Kai (masculine)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This show signal handily helped me so much when going through life. Throughout this show, we see Eli who was an introvert, hated himself, and was constantly bullied by his appearance with his cleft lip until he took the tough love advice from Johnny Lawrence and grabbed life by the balls and turning the tables that he has the power, while not waiting for anyone to make a change for himself.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You see that… Doesn’t matter if you’re a loser, or a nerd, or a freak… all that matters is that you become BADASS!” — Johnny Lawrence&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does it really mean to “Flip the Script”?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, I see it as looking at your strengths instead of the weakness we may pay attention too much, which leads to self doubt, fears, and self-fulfilling prophecy. Acknowledge the weakness, and use that to your advantage. So face that dragon whatever it maybe (ie. taking action towards that girl you like, in a fight or competition, etc.) while going in with it that the script that life give us you may see as a disadvantage, though now looking at it with a different perspective and lenses to now it’s your advantage.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=RO6GPt6xbv8&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 3 (2021)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Willing to fight smart whether its an opponent, or the adversity through life.
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=https:&#x2F;&#x2F;youtu.be&#x2F;haRKrSfKVg0?feature=shared&amp;t=42&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me let you in a little secret. It’s not just the haircut, or the back tattoo, it’s the way of life man. You just gotta feel the energy and live in the moment.” — Eli Moskowitz aka Hawk&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hawk himself doesn’t realize he is applying the philosophy with yang of flowing, being able to move freely physically and mentally, while we see Demetri acting stiff and awkward. He is in the flow state, like what Bruce Lee meant while being like water.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kxZZlk1mK0VBKX88lDuU-g.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If I want to punch, I’m gonna do it man” — Bruce Lee&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water is never stiff, it moves and flows without any judgement or second thoughts to do said things. It adapts to it’s environment while being one with it, without the conscious thinking of doubt that we usually do. When you try to punch or hurt water, it doesn’t react and instead embodies the hit. While it being the most softest element, at the same time, it can penetrate a rock or slice through metal. And the fact that we are 70% made up of water as well. Water is liquid consciousness. I think this philosophy and the things that are taught in the Tao, is more towards, Miyagi Do’s ways of teaching compared to Cobra Kai’s “Strike first, strike hard.” mentality, balance of these two is needed. Like Bruce Lee said, wanting to strike a punch (Cobra Kai’s philosophy) while being comfortable in one own skin, with no judgment (Miyagi Do’s philosophy), this is what Hawk does while being at the party and will also learn more of later on in Season 4.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another character Demetri, who is best friends of Hawk, has the same trouble of standing up for himself, self doubt, and self fulfilling prophecies that turns against him. Instead of him going to Cobra Kai like Hawk did, he went to Miyagi Do where he did seek the same aspects and philosophy though in a way of a balance and self inner peace. His development overtime happened slow and gradually compared to Hawk’s transformation through within Season 3, he as well “Flipped the Script”.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=Z919pABSkQo&amp;t=1161s&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Demetri&#x27;s ark&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
In the video, Demetri’s Dating Advice (Cobra Kai Analysis) by Watch Party, I think we can all relate with our brain power and imagination taking the control in situations where we may find it out of our comfort zone. Overtime, in the series, Demetri uses his brain power and imagination, as the upper hand while putting self beliefs that changes his script in life for the good. And he “Flipped the Script” towards the girl he liked, Yasmine, to get her interested within him by unconsciously planting the seed by her writing it down. (Kinda like Inception)
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kiORtWdH6Hr3TcdA5Q5pVQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;yasmine&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
Life is all about perspective. So apply “Flipping the Script” into your own life in each creative way, as long it is with good intent and is uplifting yourself and others to be greater. “With great power, comes great responsibility” — Uncle Ben.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gRbe5RRCfy3xxc2gzaj6ZQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee Quotes&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;You are your own self fulgilling prophecy&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Welp, that’s my take on it, and while your at it, go learn a martial arts if you haven’t already to grasp this concept even more. Until then, don’t stop being a badass.
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Divde and Conquer by the Elites. FREE YOUR MIND | WHEN WILL WE COME TOGETHER?</title>
        <published>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-03-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/come-together/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;external-content.duckduckgo.com&amp;#x2F;iu&amp;#x2F;?u=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FOBwuHLkqgKM%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg&amp;amp;f=1&amp;amp;nofb=1&amp;amp;ipt=b34b3cb2d46e67c01fc0007f26baf1e2a7d4fe8620b67e523575b40f2f71b8cd&amp;amp;ipo=images&quot; alt=&quot;civil war&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I knew I couldn’t kill them. More powerful men than me have tried. But if I could get them to kill eachother…” - Zemo.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SEE THROUGH THE ILLUSION AND THE AGENDA THAT IS BEING WAGED ON US. All of these hate crimes on the news and mainstream is to DIVIDE AND CONQUER US. They dont want us coming TOGETHER as a community and putting our differences to the side! If that were to happen, we’ll be too powerful than these higher ups and puppet on a string! They got us FIGHTING EACH OTHER instead of us fighting these “elites” whos doing this to us in the first place! See the repeated tactics they use against us. 9&#x2F;11, racially divide and hate towards Musilms creating a false flag to put us in control. Now with this pandemic, racial division again towards the black community, get us rally up, go against our neighbor, killing each other. Now more false flags on Asians and creating illusions by the media. We already know who is responsible for this whole “pandemic” in the first place! Research Event 201, these cover boys like Bill Gates, Fauci, Joe Biden, Trump etc. Is being controlled by the numbers, rituals, etc.! Hint: all roads lead to Rome. Like how in Captain America Civil War, the spilt of the Avengers was detrimental and came with consequences of that spilt. Fighting each other instead of looking at whos behind the scenes pulling the strings! They DON’T WANT US COMING TOGETHER! IF WE DO ITS OVER FOR THEM! THEY DEPEND ON US! WE HAVE THE POWER! Why you think they enslaved us? GovernMENT! Govern the MENTAL, THE MIND 🧠. This is a phycological warfare that their doing on us! KNOW THAT YOU HAVE THE POWER! Don’t fight your neighbor. He’s not the enemy. #FreeYourMind&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
