<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - Rap</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/rap/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/rap/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Vultures 1 Album Review</title>
        <published>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-02-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/vultures-1-album-review/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;cdn.discordapp.com&amp;#x2F;attachments&amp;#x2F;1112522475788566629&amp;#x2F;1206765359546241085&amp;#x2F;Screenshot_20240211-165847.jpg?ex=65dd32d2&amp;amp;is=65cabdd2&amp;amp;hm=60a57d9b89a741fe1062aa856f46dbed27724ea3f35be62c0c37d4b89c9ef983&amp;amp;&quot; alt=&quot;Vultures 1&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After many delays Kanye West next collabration album with Ty Dolla $ign is here with the first volume of the Vultures trilogy. My opinions on the album is that there are some songs on here that are a miss for me and should’ve been cut out, replaced, or needed more fixing on, there is a lot of hits for me that makes the album enjoyable still. This project feels like a combination of Kanye’s past albums and eras that is sprinkled in the songs that I enjoyed the most, which I was totally surprised that he would go back to those sounds, ranging from the 2000s era with the College trilogy and 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreaks, to the 2010s era with MBDTF, Yeezus, TLOP, and much more. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt; First Act of VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
Right out with the intro, with STARS, is a really well done introduction to the album with really good drums which I assume JPEGMAFIA worked on for the intro as its really dynamic. Throughout the 1st act of the album, there are some songs that I didn&#x27;t really enjoy like KEYS TO MY LIFE AND HOODRAT but the rest of the 1st act like PAID, TALKING, BACK TO ME, DO IT. The disco&#x2F;dance and EDM aspect for the album like PAID AND DO IT is really executed well. I esspecially liked the violins and strings sounds in DO IT. 
&lt;h1&gt;Second Act of VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
Now the second act is my favorite part of the album starting with PAPERWORK, with its experimental aspects and distorted bass and drums, which has that YEEZUS sound really shine in this album with experimental voxstoo. And we transition from that experimental sound to straight 2000s nostalgic Kanye era. Now BURN takes the cake for being my most favorite track out of this album, with Kanye bringing back that classic flow and the amazing chorus that sounds like it&#x27;s a predecessor from his other song that last time we got this type of style of a song from him, White Dress. BURN makes me feel like I&#x27;m in sometype of cinematic Martial Arts&#x2F;Bruce Lee&#x2F;Quentin Tarantino movie type of vibe. This track is overall fun, soulful and simplistic but sounds amazing. I feel like if JPEGMAFIA helped produced this track, combinding soulful with a little bit more of experimental sounds and seeing how well that goes together. Would be something different I&#x27;ll like to see next time if Kanye or anyone (or even me) combines the two like that. The only con for this song is that its too short, ending at 1:51 minutes. Could&#x27;ve been more extended I feel. Though I do hope Kanye brings more of this sounds and make an album surrounded by the idea of BURN and White Dress. Then the next track FUK SUMN, goes back into that experimental hip-hop, with again, JPEGMAFIA helping producing this track with the chipmuck high pitch Kanye vocal sample and the complex drum patterns. After FUCK SUMN we go into the single with VULTURES, which when listening to the first version of it back in 2023, I didn&#x27;t really liked it at all, I thought it was too basic with the beat and the production, lyrics were okay though, the song has grown on me, but for sure not the best on this album when its competing other better songs mentioning before. With CARNIVAL, I love the choir sample having more of a Middle Eastern sounding throughout this song, with again more experimental trap. A little too dark with my taste as I don&#x27;t really like Playboi Carti&#x27;s music at all because of that. But still a hype type of song neither the less. 
&lt;h1&gt;Third act of the VULTURES 1&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
With GOOD (DON&#x27;T DIE) is an absolute skip for me. Should&#x27;ve been cut and sounds like it needs more fixed on. It sures has 808s &amp; Heartbreaks sounding to it but to me wasn&#x27;t executed very well along with the singing and vocals sounded like it needs improvement. The last two songs in the third act is a lot better with BEG FORGIVENESS and KING. I also liked the sample chopping in the 3:39 mark of the song with BEG FORGIVENESS and has better singing. And again with KING, the drums in the production is amazing, and the line with &quot;Crazy, bipolar, antisemite&quot; makes me laugh with the way Kanye says it. Overall, I enjoyed this album despite it being flawed in many aspects, it somewhat feels like an album that is jotting down many ideas, concepts and genres with really strong ideas and ones that don&#x27;t work. Maybe that will be fixed in VULTURES 2 &amp; 3. 
&lt;h1&gt;Favorite Tracks&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BURN&lt;&#x2F;li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;FUCK SUMN&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TALKING&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAPERWORK&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DO IT&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STARS&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PAID&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CARNIVAL&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BACK TO ME&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BEG FORGIVENESS&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KING&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Least Favorite Tracks&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GOOD (GOOD DON&#x27;T DIE)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HOODRAT&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KEYS TO MY LIFE&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VULTURES&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Final Verdict&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7&#x2F;10&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>How Hip-Hop became my Threapy</title>
        <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*Exdv8YZ-61wvNOekU9DPHg.png&quot; alt=&quot;hiphopimage&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me. This lead me to the point of finding a healthy outlet and some ways to face my shadows within me that I was dealing with that were brought up during these events with her. During our separation, I found that I loved making music and making my own lyrics on how I felt with everything that was happening in my personal life. There were always just notes on my phone and never really tried to rap or anything, until around later that year, where I made two rap songs. After always being inspired by the world of rapping, poetry, etc. I finally took action on what I wanted to do for a while since the beginning of that year. In 2021, I still had those wounds on what happened as I never really listened to songs that resonated on how I felt since, I didn’t wanted to feel negative. I realized that this was an act of spiritual bypassing as I didn’t want to acknowledge myself truly and as a person who both have light and dark aspects, which we all have. I particularly dived in more into the world of Hip-Hop, finding new artists, songs, sub-genre, style, etc. with the subject matter of vulnerability and heartbreak. Albums and songs that I listened to, that got me through those times and still is to this day. A sense of a feeling that shows how Hip-Hop evolved so much to express one self. With Hip-Hop&#x2F;Rap as well being a mostly masculine trait, it shows how it is to be a man and at the same time not shunning those inner feelings within us and vent it in a way of an art form. You could see this within rap artist Kayne West, who revolutionized of showing ones emotions within the world of Hip-Hop with his album, 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak rather just Hip-Hop on the topic just gangsters, money, sex and drugs all the time, and open the doors to everyone to rap no matter where they come from and don’t have to be a certain way to always act tough, aggressive, violent, they can be comfortable within their own skins. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=J_CT8dy2mlc&amp;t=766s&quot;&gt; &lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;The Impact of 808s &amp; Heartbreaks&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a therapist costing a lot, and my own self therapy by reflection, learning psychology and the shadow self while listening to Hip-Hop music the tackles vulnerable topics that I can deeply relate to and a sense that I’m not alone on what I’m going through. After this, it got me inspired to make more of my own music, lyrics and full expression without judgement along with freestyling, which really feels like another way for me to meditate and a sense of being very spiritual as rapping, deals with one of the higher chakras, the throat chakra as you get this spiritual bliss while doing it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some recommended albums that helped me through during my separation:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brockhampton — Ginger &#x2F; RoadRunner: New Lights, New Machine &#x2F; Saturation &#x2F; Saturation II &#x2F; Saturation III&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadeca — From Me to You &#x2F; From Me to You (Deluxe)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayne West — KIDS SEE GHOSTS &#x2F; 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak &#x2F; My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jaden — SYRE &#x2F; ERYS &#x2F; The Sunset Tapes: A Cool Tape Story&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Cole — 4 Your Eyez Only &#x2F; Born Sinner&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joey Bada$$ — 2000&#x2F;1999&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Koi — before it’s too late&#x2F; 10&amp;amp;2&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Brian — The Sailor&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse(Soundtrack From &amp;amp; Inspired by the Motion Picture)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than that, check out my music on&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;open.spotify.com&#x2F;artist&#x2F;1ojpTukPyY4MaB7tseXdtQ&quot;&gt; Spotify,&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.soundcloud.com&#x2F;PhantomBroken&quot;&gt;SoundCloud&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;@PhantomBroken&quot;&gt; YouTube&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; that I’m making and support it if you like it! Also starting a movement with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;peterparkercode.github.io&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hip-hop-and-threapy&#x2F;.&#x2F;clga&quot;&gt;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; instead of the parental advisory logo and wanting Hip-Hop music to go against the agendas that’s been going on in this world&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*xGdyYyKGfdOAQPBjXu1AMw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gcjU-7dLV_HT0vkWqnI8cA.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY sticker&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Down the image to add to your song art covers!&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*VV-VB3jGenl_oBkuFqxPDw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CLGA&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
