<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - Asia</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/asia/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/asia/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>MoonBin K-pop Star Dead Gematria Decoded</title>
        <published>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/2023-21-04-moonbin-gematria/">&lt;p&gt;The days between Kim Jong-hyun death to moon bin his exactly 74 months apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like how 47 the reflection of 74 as Suicide = 47&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moon bin = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ritual Sacrifice = 107&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The concert Moonbin was supposed to attend called Dream Concert equals to 56 and 205 as he died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The record label that Astro is with Fatagio equates to 44 like kill = 44 in gematria and how he died on a Wednesday equating to 44 in the same Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asian also equates to 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kpop idol = 44&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Kpop group Astro equates to 19, as he died on the 19th of April as Moonbin and Astro also equating to 35 in Reverse Reduction&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the Moon cycle is every 19 years&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chaos = 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19 hijackers in 9&#x2F;11 to Covid-19 in 2019&#x2F;early 2020&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and even Kpop star = 35 and 46 as well with sacrifice = 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And 4&#x2F;19&#x2F;23 has a date numerology of 46&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From his last birthday 1&#x2F;26&#x2F;23 to his death is exactly 83 days, as Murder = 83 and so is Seoul South Korea = 83. Also to note he died on the anniversary of the movie Murder by Numbers&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also noticed that the Astro logo looks like the Star of David&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;what clues they are trying to hint at is something related to space and astrology, with his name being Moonbin&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TST Yohan death to Moonbin is 44 weeks apart&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also died at the age of 25&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli and Moonbin both have the gematria of 35&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sulli also equates to 19&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His death occurred during Space X ship exploding, with the theme revolving around space, the moon, astrology, etc.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Astro color scheme is purple as Prince color was purple as this occurred very closely to Prince death&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
