<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title> - Medium Archives</title>
    <subtitle>A minimalist Zola theme that prioritizes clean CSS and avoids heavy JavaScript. Enjoy a seamless user experience with lightning-fast load times. Let your content take center stage in a clutter-free, elegant design that enhances readability. Responsive and efficient, anemone brings focus to your ideas.</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/medium-archives/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/tags/medium-archives/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>How Hip-Hop became my Threapy</title>
        <published>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/hip-hop-and-threapy/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*Exdv8YZ-61wvNOekU9DPHg.png&quot; alt=&quot;hiphopimage&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About two years ago, I was in a separation with this girl that I liked, which was sadly cut off too shortly after major agendas were taking place around the world. A lot of grief, mourning, heartbreak took place with a lot elephants in the room needing to be addressed between me and her, as I tried to reach out to her, though she became very distant, closed off and avoided me. This lead me to the point of finding a healthy outlet and some ways to face my shadows within me that I was dealing with that were brought up during these events with her. During our separation, I found that I loved making music and making my own lyrics on how I felt with everything that was happening in my personal life. There were always just notes on my phone and never really tried to rap or anything, until around later that year, where I made two rap songs. After always being inspired by the world of rapping, poetry, etc. I finally took action on what I wanted to do for a while since the beginning of that year. In 2021, I still had those wounds on what happened as I never really listened to songs that resonated on how I felt since, I didn’t wanted to feel negative. I realized that this was an act of spiritual bypassing as I didn’t want to acknowledge myself truly and as a person who both have light and dark aspects, which we all have. I particularly dived in more into the world of Hip-Hop, finding new artists, songs, sub-genre, style, etc. with the subject matter of vulnerability and heartbreak. Albums and songs that I listened to, that got me through those times and still is to this day. A sense of a feeling that shows how Hip-Hop evolved so much to express one self. With Hip-Hop&#x2F;Rap as well being a mostly masculine trait, it shows how it is to be a man and at the same time not shunning those inner feelings within us and vent it in a way of an art form. You could see this within rap artist Kayne West, who revolutionized of showing ones emotions within the world of Hip-Hop with his album, 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak rather just Hip-Hop on the topic just gangsters, money, sex and drugs all the time, and open the doors to everyone to rap no matter where they come from and don’t have to be a certain way to always act tough, aggressive, violent, they can be comfortable within their own skins. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=J_CT8dy2mlc&amp;t=766s&quot;&gt; &lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;The Impact of 808s &amp; Heartbreaks&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a therapist costing a lot, and my own self therapy by reflection, learning psychology and the shadow self while listening to Hip-Hop music the tackles vulnerable topics that I can deeply relate to and a sense that I’m not alone on what I’m going through. After this, it got me inspired to make more of my own music, lyrics and full expression without judgement along with freestyling, which really feels like another way for me to meditate and a sense of being very spiritual as rapping, deals with one of the higher chakras, the throat chakra as you get this spiritual bliss while doing it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some recommended albums that helped me through during my separation:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brockhampton — Ginger &#x2F; RoadRunner: New Lights, New Machine &#x2F; Saturation &#x2F; Saturation II &#x2F; Saturation III&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quadeca — From Me to You &#x2F; From Me to You (Deluxe)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kayne West — KIDS SEE GHOSTS &#x2F; 808s &amp;amp; Heartbreak &#x2F; My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jaden — SYRE &#x2F; ERYS &#x2F; The Sunset Tapes: A Cool Tape Story&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;J. Cole — 4 Your Eyez Only &#x2F; Born Sinner&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joey Bada$$ — 2000&#x2F;1999&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Koi — before it’s too late&#x2F; 10&amp;amp;2&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rich Brian — The Sailor&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse(Soundtrack From &amp;amp; Inspired by the Motion Picture)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than that, check out my music on&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;open.spotify.com&#x2F;artist&#x2F;1ojpTukPyY4MaB7tseXdtQ&quot;&gt; Spotify,&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.soundcloud.com&#x2F;PhantomBroken&quot;&gt;SoundCloud&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;@PhantomBroken&quot;&gt; YouTube&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; that I’m making and support it if you like it! Also starting a movement with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;peterparkercode.github.io&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hip-hop-and-threapy&#x2F;.&#x2F;clga&quot;&gt;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; instead of the parental advisory logo and wanting Hip-Hop music to go against the agendas that’s been going on in this world&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*xGdyYyKGfdOAQPBjXu1AMw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gcjU-7dLV_HT0vkWqnI8cA.png&quot; alt=&quot;CONSCIOUS LYRICS, GOVERNMENT ADVISORY sticker&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Down the image to add to your song art covers!&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*VV-VB3jGenl_oBkuFqxPDw.png&quot; alt=&quot;CLGA&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Flipping the Script (Cobra Kai Philosophy)</title>
        <published>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/cobra-kai/">&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=yZFBtHG3okI&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*FwO48aT4QmUIQmZj9lMPmQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;ying yang&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;The balance between Miyagi Do (feminine) and Cobra Kai (masculine)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This show signal handily helped me so much when going through life. Throughout this show, we see Eli who was an introvert, hated himself, and was constantly bullied by his appearance with his cleft lip until he took the tough love advice from Johnny Lawrence and grabbed life by the balls and turning the tables that he has the power, while not waiting for anyone to make a change for himself.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You see that… Doesn’t matter if you’re a loser, or a nerd, or a freak… all that matters is that you become BADASS!” — Johnny Lawrence&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does it really mean to “Flip the Script”?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, I see it as looking at your strengths instead of the weakness we may pay attention too much, which leads to self doubt, fears, and self-fulfilling prophecy. Acknowledge the weakness, and use that to your advantage. So face that dragon whatever it maybe (ie. taking action towards that girl you like, in a fight or competition, etc.) while going in with it that the script that life give us you may see as a disadvantage, though now looking at it with a different perspective and lenses to now it’s your advantage.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=RO6GPt6xbv8&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 3 (2021)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Willing to fight smart whether its an opponent, or the adversity through life.
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=https:&#x2F;&#x2F;youtu.be&#x2F;haRKrSfKVg0?feature=shared&amp;t=42&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Cobra Kai Season 1(2018)&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let me let you in a little secret. It’s not just the haircut, or the back tattoo, it’s the way of life man. You just gotta feel the energy and live in the moment.” — Eli Moskowitz aka Hawk&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hawk himself doesn’t realize he is applying the philosophy with yang of flowing, being able to move freely physically and mentally, while we see Demetri acting stiff and awkward. He is in the flow state, like what Bruce Lee meant while being like water.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kxZZlk1mK0VBKX88lDuU-g.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If I want to punch, I’m gonna do it man” — Bruce Lee&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Water is never stiff, it moves and flows without any judgement or second thoughts to do said things. It adapts to it’s environment while being one with it, without the conscious thinking of doubt that we usually do. When you try to punch or hurt water, it doesn’t react and instead embodies the hit. While it being the most softest element, at the same time, it can penetrate a rock or slice through metal. And the fact that we are 70% made up of water as well. Water is liquid consciousness. I think this philosophy and the things that are taught in the Tao, is more towards, Miyagi Do’s ways of teaching compared to Cobra Kai’s “Strike first, strike hard.” mentality, balance of these two is needed. Like Bruce Lee said, wanting to strike a punch (Cobra Kai’s philosophy) while being comfortable in one own skin, with no judgment (Miyagi Do’s philosophy), this is what Hawk does while being at the party and will also learn more of later on in Season 4.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another character Demetri, who is best friends of Hawk, has the same trouble of standing up for himself, self doubt, and self fulfilling prophecies that turns against him. Instead of him going to Cobra Kai like Hawk did, he went to Miyagi Do where he did seek the same aspects and philosophy though in a way of a balance and self inner peace. His development overtime happened slow and gradually compared to Hawk’s transformation through within Season 3, he as well “Flipped the Script”.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;
src=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.youtube.com&#x2F;watch?v=Z919pABSkQo&amp;t=1161s&quot;&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;iframe&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Demetri&#x27;s ark&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
In the video, Demetri’s Dating Advice (Cobra Kai Analysis) by Watch Party, I think we can all relate with our brain power and imagination taking the control in situations where we may find it out of our comfort zone. Overtime, in the series, Demetri uses his brain power and imagination, as the upper hand while putting self beliefs that changes his script in life for the good. And he “Flipped the Script” towards the girl he liked, Yasmine, to get her interested within him by unconsciously planting the seed by her writing it down. (Kinda like Inception)
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:720&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*kiORtWdH6Hr3TcdA5Q5pVQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;yasmine&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
Life is all about perspective. So apply “Flipping the Script” into your own life in each creative way, as long it is with good intent and is uplifting yourself and others to be greater. “With great power, comes great responsibility” — Uncle Ben.
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*gRbe5RRCfy3xxc2gzaj6ZQ.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Bruce Lee Quotes&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;You are your own self fulgilling prophecy&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
Welp, that’s my take on it, and while your at it, go learn a martial arts if you haven’t already to grasp this concept even more. Until then, don’t stop being a badass.
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>We Always Have a Choice</title>
        <published>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-08-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/"/>
        <id>https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://peterparkercode.github.io/blog/we-always-have-a-choice/">&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*e74uJ-7Th6ow9m3ZXu9pTA.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 1&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Source:Ultimate Spider-Man Comic&lt;&#x2F;h5&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*D1h9p9Xvdd8W73hxUiddGg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 2&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:1100&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*T9OeDOH5Bq8tT-PGNCMQEg.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 3&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With great power, there must also come — great responsibility.” No matter what in life, we always have a choice to make the right decisions, even if it feels like we’re forced to do said things that doesn’t resonate with us and know that is not the best option. We have the choice to not only to make the right decisions for ourselves, but for others and for the sake of the betterment of humanity. With so many things that happened these past years of shambles not only in our personal lives, though the whole world needing to heal. We all have that power within us to change for the good. I also think the reason why till this day, I still love Spider-Man, is that the more I get older, the lessons within those stories that I read, watch, or play, makes more sense to me. Peter Parker, someone who took his powers for granted, using it in ways of for his own gain and not for the people around him as he had the choice to stop that robber, though didn’t, which led to the death of Uncle Ben. With every choice we make, comes with a certain strength and power. Only thing is, how would we use it?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;miro.medium.com&amp;#x2F;v2&amp;#x2F;resize:fit:640&amp;#x2F;format:webp&amp;#x2F;1*HDp005Id05BSXeqXRwLSrw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Comicbook 3&quot;&gt;
  
&lt;&#x2F;div&gt;</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
